A Guide to the Kilmarnock Baptist Church (Lancaster County, Va.) records, 2012-2018
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Kilmarnock Baptist Church (Lancaster County, Va.) records, 2012-2018
The Library of Virginia
52594
.35 cu. ft. and 1 box
Kilmarnock Baptist Church (Lancaster County, Va.)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Steve Gallimore, Kilmarnock, Virginia.
Historical Information
Kilmarnock Baptist Church is located in Kilmarnock, Lancaster County, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Records, 2012-2018, of Kilmarnock Baptist Church in Lancaster County, Virginia, consisting of booklets, budget drafts, bulletins, correspondence, directories, flyers, and newsletters highlighting the activities and worship opportunities of the church.
Contents List
- Directory, 2012 (Folder 1)
- Directory, 2015 (Folder 2)
- Directory, 2016 (Folder 3)
- Newsletter, March 2017 (Folder 4)
- Newsletter, september 2017 (Folder 5)
- Newsletter, October 2017 (Folder 6)
- Newsletter, December 2017 (Folder 7)
- Newsletter, January 2018 (Folder 8)
- Newsletter, February 2018 (Folder 9)
- Newsletter, March 2018 (Folder 10)
- Newsletter, April 2018 (Folder 11)
- Newsletter, May 2018 (Folder 12)
- Newsletter, June 2018 (Folder 13)
- Newsletter, July 2018 (Folder 14)
- Newsletter, August 2018 (Folder 15)
- Newsletter, October 2018 (Folder 16)
- Bulletins, January 2017 (Folder 17)
- Bulletins, February 2017 (Folder 18)
- Bulletins, March 2017 (Folder 19)
- Bulletins, April 2017 (Folder 20)
- Bulletins, May 2017 (Folder 21)
- Bulletins, June 2017 (Folder 22)
- Bulletins, July 2017 (Folder 23)
- Bulletins, August 2017 (Folder 24)
- Bulletins, September 2017 (Folder 25)
- Bulletins, October 2017 (Folder 26)
- Bulletins, November 2017 (Folder 27)
- Bulletins, December 2017 (Folder 28)
- Bulletins, January 2018 (Folder 29)
- Bulletins, February 2018 (Folder 30)
- Bulletins, March 2018 (Folder 31)
- Bulletins, April 2018 (Folder 32)
- Bulletins, May 2018 (Folder 33)
- Bulletins, June 2018 (Folder 34)
- Bulletins, July 2018 (Folder 35)
- Bulletins, August 2018 (Folder 36)
- Bulletins, September 2018 (Folder 37)
- Bulletins, October 2018 (Folder 38)
- Bulletins, November 2018 (Folder 39)
- Dr. James Benson Johnson acceptance letter and resume, 11 June 2018 (Folder 40)
- Draft of proposed 2019 budget, 4 October 2018 (Folder 41)
- Prayers of the People: Cooperative Baptist Fellowship's Yearlong Guide to Prayer, 2016-2017 (Folder 42)
- Cooperative Baptist Fellowship global mission fliers (Folder 43)